   [
    {
      "question": "How many total types of scanning in cyber security?",
      "choice1": "1",
      "choice2": "2",
      "choice3": "3",
      "choice4": "4",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the first computer virus among the following",
      "choice1": "Blaster",
      "choice2": "creeper",
      "choice3": "Sasser",
      "choice4": "Both 2 and 3",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which protocol is mostly used in Wi-fi security?",
      "choice1": "WPS",
      "choice2": "WPA",
      "choice3": "WPA2",
      "choice4": "both 2 and 3",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which malware does not replicate or clone through an infection?",
      "choice1": "Worms",
      "choice2": "Trojans",
      "choice3": "Rookits",
      "choice4": "Virus",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the legal form of hacking",
      "choice1": "Craking",
      "choice2": "Non-ethical hacking",
      "choice3": "Ethical hacking",
      "choice4": "Hacktivism",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Malware stands for?",
      "choice1": "Multipurpose software",
      "choice2": "Malfunctioned software",
      "choice3": "Malfunctioning of security",
      "choice4": "Malicious software",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which security protocol is not strong?",
      "choice1": "SMTP",
      "choice2": "SSL",
      "choice3": "SFTP",
      "choice4": "HTTPS",
      "answer": 1
    },
 
    {
      "question": "PCT stands for ______",
      "choice1": "Private Communication Technique",
      "choice2": "Private Connecting Technology ",
      "choice3": "Private Communication Technology",
      "choice4": "Personal Communication Technology",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the first phase of ethical hacking?",
      "choice1": "Footprinting",
      "choice2": "ARP Poisoning",
      "choice3": "DNS Poisoning",
      "choice4": "Eumeration",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Why proxy serveris used by hacker?",
      "choice1": "For obtaining remote access connection",
      "choice2": "Hiding malicious activity on the network",
      "choice3": "Create a ghost server ona network",
      "choice4": "create a stornger connection with the target",
      "answer": 2
    }
  ]